interface Card {
    front: string;
    back: string;
}

// Create an array of cards
export const cards: Card[] = [
    { front: "Apple", back: "사과" },
    { front: "Banana", back: "바나나" },
    { front: "Cat", back: "고양이" },
    { front: "Dog", back: "개" },
    { front: "Elephant", back: "코끼리" },
    { front: "Fish", back: "물고기" },
    { front: "Giraffe", back: "기린" },
    { front: "Horse", back: "말" },
    { front: "Penguin", back: "펭귄" },
    { front: "Duck", back: "오리" },
    { front: "Bear", back: "곰" },
    { front: "Rabbit", back: "토끼" },
    { front: "Tiger", back: "호랑이" },
    { front: "Wolf", back: "늑대" },
];